Karim Gamal

ARCHITECT & INTERIOR DESIGN

- **Section** Gkarim444@gmail.com
- **U** 01067190256
- Egypt , El-Menoufia , Menouf
- **⇒** 9th July 1992
- ർ Married
- **♦** Final Exemption
- Profile Facebook
- O Profile Instagram

SKILLS

AutoCAD 2D	• • • • •
Revit Architecture	• • • •
3DS Max & Vray	• • • •
Adobe Photoshop	• • • •
Microsoft Office	• • • •

LANGUAGES

Arabic	• • • • •
English	• • • • •

PROFILE

Architect with 8 years of experience in planning, building construction and implementation. I have experience in dealing with multiple projects at the same time and completing them in record time. Good experience in dealing with clients and companies.

EDUCATION

Architectural Engineering Bachelor, Menoufia University

2009 – 2014 | Shibin El Kom, Egypt

- Overall rating: 75.5% Very good
- Graduation project: very good

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Founder and owner of Arcala Engineering Consultancy

2017 – present | Menouf, Egypt Arcala Page on Facebook *⊗*

Architect Engineer at Engineering Consulting Office

July 2016 – December 2016 Menouf, Egypt

Architect Engineer at General Contracting Company

July 2015 – July 2016 | Menouf, Egypt